ALL NAMES, CHARACTERS,
AND EVENTS ARE FICTIONAL
CHILD AND ANIMAL WELFARE
REGULATIONS WERE OBSERVED
It's what I'm good at.
It's
ruining something.
This time,
it will be you.
Nonsense.
It's total nonsense.
WINTER OF 2008
If I change first, I can change the world?
The truth is,
the world blames me for changing alone.
The very world that
they've been blaming for not changing.
Do you know
why my father crushed you completely?
Because you were sincere.
The real deal.
He was afraid that people would see that.
That's why.
The activists who wander
from protest to protest
and politicians who prowl
around the election scene don't have that.
You actually came from the working class,
and you were fighting for your colleagues
who were wrongfully injured.
It was only a matter of time
before people realized
that you were the real deal.
Like you said, it's been 20 years.
Do you know
why Haseong still supports my father?
Even if it was only a towel,
he'd visit those
living beyond the reach of cars,
offering them one by one
and asking how they are doing.
That sincerity touches people's hearts
and makes him win.
You may buy votes with your slogan,
but not their hearts.
To win their hearts,
you have to be sincere.
And you
already have the sincerity.
Only you don't know
how powerful it is.
Gosh, it's freezing.
Oh, you were here.
Why are you two together?
If you were going to drink,
you should've called me.
You know I crave alcohol
after I work overtime…
H CHEMICAL'S ILLEGAL SUCCESSION OUT
H CHEMICAL
HASEONG FACTORY
NO ENTRY
FACTORY CLOSED DUE TO FIRE INCIDENT
1,488 DAYS WITHOUT AN ACCIDENT
KEEP OUT
RISK OF COLLAPSE
…COMES BEFORE CORPORATE PROFIT
DANGER
KEEP OUT
Wow.
Where did you get these?
From the sauna locker room?
What? Is it a trade secret?
All right. One, two, three…
Here. 30,000 won.
Are you done being a fangirl now?
Good thinking.
My life's so messed up,
everyone around me is Cha Su-yeon's fan.
And they're all living miserable lives.
Enough with the nonsense
and give me 20,000 won more.
So you're not mute.
Here. 50,000 won.
It's a full set. You're good.
MR. BUYER
Hello, sir.
Now?
Sure, no problem.
Just send me where you want to meet.
I'll bring the stuff over right away.
I didn't see the necklace that I gave you.
Maybe Lee Hwa-jin stole it?
She was ransacking this place
without turning the lights on.
-Hello.
-Hello. Open it.
Take it.
Thank you.
There's one more.
This way.
-This way, please.
-Thanks.
Wait.
Could you tell me a little bit
about this person who wanted to see me?
Did the chairman not mention anything?
I was just told it's a woman in her 20s.
Come this way.
Okay.
Hello, nice to meet you.
I'm Choi Myeong-ju.
I heard you wanted some special outfits,
so I brought a few.
You can try them on before you decide…
Let's divorce.
Keep your eyes closed.
Okay.
One second.
Now, open your eyes.
Ta-da.
Congrats on your admission, Ji-yu.
You're going to high school now.
Do you like it?
Mom.
Are you sure I can wear this?
It's the only thing you wanted
from what I have.
Are you sure?
Of course.
But school starts in one month.
One month will fly by.
Mom, but I--
Why? Keep it on.
So Dad can see it when he's home.
I want this as a gift for graduation,
not for starting school.
What?
I love this.
I really love it,
but I'll love it
even more if I get it when I turn 20.
When you turn 20?
Yes.
No, that's insane.
You turning 20?
Come on. Three years will fly by.
So please keep it safe until then.
Maybe Lee Hwa-jin stole it?
She was ransacking this place
without turning the lights on.
Please enter the passcode.
Safe unlocked.
Safe door open.
YU JIN-MYEONG
APRIL 4, 2012
Ms. Cha.
I went to Chairman Yang's vacation home
to see his special guest today.
And guess who I met there.
Hwa-jin. Lee Hwa-jin!
HASEONG HIGH SCHOOL
HASEONG HIGH SCHOOL RAISES TALENT
THROUGH A HEALTHY MIND AND BODY
ANNOUNCEMENT OF THE RESULTS
OF THE SCHOOL VIOLENCE CASE
Allegations that President-elect's wife,
Cha, exerted pressure
to block the convening
of the school violence committee
have been proven false.
Stating that Ko and Park,
who filmed and shared the video,
habitually committed acts of violence
and used the footage to threaten them,
their victims have filed
a criminal complaint.
That's the question.
Doesn't this remind you of a formula?
It's…
Hi, Ji-yu.
Go and sit.
Let's continue. Focus.
This question should remind you
of the formula.
We talked about this
in the last class, guys.
Focus.
Focus, okay?
This comes up a lot on exams.
Now, plus three…
What do you mean?
You don't want to go study abroad?
I'm not going.
I'm not going to run away.
Ji-yu, this can be hard for you.
I told you.
Even if the same thing happens,
I'll fight her again.
The fact that Dad's president now
changed your world,
not mine.
I want to stay in my world.
I'll fight in my world.
So don't use me as an excuse.
You just do what you want.
If you want to divorce him, divorce him.
If you want to fight, fight.
Just apply the modified formula.
Now, what is X plus Y?
It's three.
X plus Y equals three.
And X multiplied by Y equals minus two.
Minus two.
Then X squared plus Y cubed…
Explain this.
You said I could count on you.
Are you okay, sir?
I'm sorry.
I only asked you
to keep Ji-yu out of trouble
in case Su-yeon tried to pull strings.
So I was going to handle it quietly.
Then she flipped out, saying I was
threatening her. What could I do?
Saying Ji-yu can't study abroad
unless she divorces me
is definitely a threat.
I thought Secretary Shin made it clear.
I offered to help you with the divorce,
and I was supposed
to get the minister position in return.
What did you say?
Wait.
Was it all Secretary Shin's decision?
Is that true?
As always,
you have such good people around you.
They do all the dirty work for you
without even being asked.
Before, it was Su-yeon,
and now, it's Secretary Shin?
Are you saying
Secretary Shin knew about this all along?
This whole plan to get Ji-yu in trouble?
Was it also Secretary Shin
who released the video?
I don't know.
All I did was
to ask the girl who filmed it
if the video was backed up to the cloud.
I can't figure out
who took the video and spread it.
And I don't need to know.
Answer my question.
Is it true that
Secretary Shin is involved?
I kept my promise, so you keep yours.
Tell me. Is it true?
This has greatly affected
my school as well.
Why do you think I took such a big risk?
I made my move
after Secretary Shin's confirmation
that she'd been delegated full authority.
I didn't know about it.
What kind of father would risk
his daughter's future like that?
It makes sense.
This felt way too risky.
See to it that Su-yeon
is handled delicately
You know what she can do
when she sets her mind to it.
She can be ruthless even to her family,
as you must've witnessed
rising to that position.
Do you want me to talk to her?
Stop meddling in our business.
And whatever Secretary Shin promised,
forget about it.
I hear Longjing tea tastes best
on the third brew.
YEAR 2012
It's nice.
Both the scent and color.
Have some.
It doesn't taste as good
as your sister's brew, though.
This is unfair.
The illegal election was Su-yeon's idea.
She plotted with Chairman Yang,
stabbed us in the back,
and even spread the rumours.
Just keep holding out.
We've still got time
until the presidential election.
If we can reveal that it was Su-yeon,
we can turn the tables.
Even if we reveal it,
I'll be the one to bear the risk.
Whether it's your fault or Su-yeon's,
the responsibility falls on me.
Because I'm your father.
I'll make my position clear at daybreak.
I'll walk away from all this.
You, too, should get out of politics
and focus on the foundation.
You can't decide this that easily.
Easily?
I've come this far
aspiring to become president.
So many of those who accused me
now hold seats in the National Assembly.
You think I decided this easily?
And what do you think I've been through?
To you, I'm not your child.
I'm either a setback or an opportunity!
You little…
Do you know what I really want to know?
Was her suicide really just a coincidence?
-What?
-I'm talking about Su-yeon's dead mother.
Stop.
Maybe someone did it to win the election!
I said, stop!
It wasn't suicide, was it?
You were right, Father.
Those people see my potential
as no bigger than a teacup.
They see me as someone
who would grovel and do whatever he's told
once handed a minister's post.
Someone easy to manipulate.
But that's not what I want.
I want to see these two scumbags
fall together.
That's always been
the only thing that I wanted.
So I should make them keep fighting.
Until the end.
Father.
You'll see.
This way, sir.
PARTY FOR PEACE AND FREEDOM
NEW VISION WITH THE SAME RESPONSIBILITY
BAE YEONG-SEON
PARTY FOR PEACE AND FREEDOM LEADER
You need time?
I thought you already agreed
to pass the special act.
Like I said,
I'm a member of my party.
I'm obliged to listen to the voices
within my party.
Please give me some time.
It sounds like time is on your side.
I heard that
the divorce agreement fell through.
There really are no secrets in this area.
Catch a whiff of blood,
then you pounce.
That's the unspoken rule in Yeouido.
I hear hell is empty.
Because all the evils are in Yeouido.
I thought once the election was over,
I could finally put an end to this.
Who do you think
shattered the party's unified position
in an instant?
At first,
I thought it was President Yu,
but I was wrong.
It was
your wife.
That can't be true.
The late Chairman Cha was
the treasurer of my party
for quite a while.
Many in my party
are entangled with him from back then,
like it or not.
And it seems that
your wife inherited the knot to them.
My wife really overturned
the party's stance overnight?
As someone
who's already been through a divorce,
let me give you some advice.
The real evils
are not in Yeouido.
They're in divorce court.
Sort out your divorce first.
The special act
comes next.
Can I still count on you to be on my side?
As your standing weakens,
Cha Su-yeon's influence will get stronger.
And I don't want that either.
My party's stance
being dictated by some private citizen
who isn't even a politician
or a party member,
that can never happen.
Does this answer your question?
Hello.
Let me talk to him briefly.
No, you may not.
I just have something to tell him.
You can't. It's our security regulations.
I know. Just for five minutes.
No, just two minutes.
Let him.
I have a suggestion.
Go ahead. I'm listening.
Your wife is now trying to connect
with people in my party.
She must be desperate.
What about you, sir?
Get to your point.
Just take the divorce to court.
I'll make sure
my party pushes the bill through.
I thought
you were Assemblywoman Bae's person.
Was I mistaken?
Before that, I was Chairman Cha's person.
And are you trying to be my person now?
How can I trust that?
It looks like
you're not as desperate as your wife.
I'm as suspicious as her.
What if I have your wife's hands tied?
Would you trust me then?
How can you reverse the party's stance
that was overturned overnight?
While Cha Su-yeon has
Chairman Cha, a dead man,
I have you, the president-elect
with a five-year term ahead.
I'll have at least twice as many
supporters in the party as she does.
Just show that
your divorce is real, not a performance.
Then reversing the party's stance
will be a piece of cake.
Why would people support you,
not Assemblywoman Bae?
So you're the one who connected my wife
to Party for Peace and Freedom.
She overturned the party's stance
through you.
And because you're like her hands in this,
it's up to you
to tie her hands or not.
You see, the first time is tough,
but the second time is easy.
Just take it to court.
Then I'll make sure
to reverse the party's stance.
On one condition, though.
I want you to take back the offer
you made to Assemblywoman Bae
for prime minister.
Assemblywoman Bae is all washed up.
I'll find someone new
who suits you better.
Are you using this
to grab power in the party?
The National Assembly election is
in less than a year.
Power in the party is power to nominate
and the first step
toward the presidential race.
You know how time flies in Yeouido.
The late Chairman Cha was
the treasurer of my party
for quite a while.
Many in my party
are entangled with him from back then,
like it or not.
And it seems that
your wife inherited the knot to them.
The inheritance my wife got
from the late Chairman Cha,
are you a part of it too?
You stayed with Party for Peace
and Freedom and became Bae's aide.
Was it also my wife's plan?
Well, I won't deny it.
But that ends here.
Your partnership with my wife.
I should walk a new path
with a new person.
Then give it some thought.
So it was really your doing?
I decided that was the only way
to get her to agree to the divorce.
You decided?
I clearly said I'd do the deciding.
You also said we didn't have time.
So you held Ji-yu against her?
And risked stigmatizing her forever?
You should attack
what would hurt her as much as hurt you.
A fight is supposed to be
dangerous and painful.
Do you even hear yourself?
You must shed blood to fight.
You can't fight without taking any blows.
You're going to keep fighting?
Once the special act is passed,
we can reveal the truth.
While Ji-yu gets hurt?
We can punish those responsible
and console unjust deaths.
While Su-yeon bleeds?
We can clear the names
of the victims-turned-wrongdoers.
You--
Wasn't that
why you got into politics?
Wasn't that why you became president?
You said this on the first day we met.
No victim should be called a wrongdoer.
YEAR 2008
Please read this.
I'll take over. You can go.
You couldn't go to the toilet
because of this, right?
What?
Yes. If I leave just for a second,
they keep clearing it away.
So I'll stay here.
You can take your time.
Still…
Hello!
Hello.
Hey!
This is against the law!
Did you register?
Is this rally registered?
Well…
A one-man protest
doesn't require a registration.
You know the law well.
But
you're bad at math.
There are two of you.
It's not a one-man protest.
Hey, call the police right now.
Tell them to take them away.
Do you see this picket?
It's fine
as long as it's one person holding it.
Check if he's right.
Yes, sir.
Since you're good at math,
you must know how to read too.
Then read this.
A laborer who worked extremely hard
to build this hotel
lost his legs from an industrial accident.
And he's in the wrong?
He was injured by professional negligence?
You can't turn a victim into a wrongdoer!
Such things must never happen!
He did not breach any law.
Seriously…
Hey.
There's two of them.
How is this a one-man protest?
I have to say
Korean law is full of holes.
It's completely messed up.
Read it!
You turned a victim into a wrongdoer!
He's being wronged!
You of all people should know!
Read it!
He was neglected for two hours!
He is permanently disabled now!
You said you'd go as far as to
divorce your wife
to get the special law passed.
The divorce was for Su-yeon.
I don't care
if it's for her or the special law.
That day, I decided
to make that divorce happen
no matter what.
You…
I decided I'd do everything that would
make trouble for you as a president.
I decided that I'd dirty my own hands
and get criticized in your place.
Why are you going this far?
Ten years ago,
when my husband died, he said
he wished the world
Gang-myeong inherited
would be different from his.
That since I was doing an important job,
I could make the world a better place.
If both you and your wife couldn't do it,
I decided to take it into my own hands.
Going this far?
I can do anything.
I can do even worse than this.
Leave.
Don't show up in front of me again.
Sorry to intrude.
You have to see this.
Your wife…
The president-elect couple's
consented divorce fell through.
Contrary to the view that the couple
would divorce by consent without a suit,
President-elect's wife Cha
officially announced
a breakdown of the consent.
Ms. Cha's lawyer
has just started a press conference.
Now, let's hear what he has to say.
What's the reason it fell through?
Even now, Ms. Cha is doing her best
to prevent the worst situation.
If you'll give us some time--
Is it the alimony or custody?
Are you saying President-elect
is at fault for the breakdown?
I heard she'd countersuit
for the president-elect's wrongdoing.
By wrongdoing, do you mean an affair?
Do you mean his affair
is the reason behind the divorce?
Is that true?
As of now,
I cannot disclose that.
You cannot disclose it, but it's true?
Then will you disclose it one day?
It would be inappropriate
to reveal it here
before the lawsuit starts.
What wrong
did the president-elect do specifically?
Are you going to reveal it strategically?
Who is he having an affair with?
What's the proof?
That'll be all for today.
Tell us more.
Is there proof?
Can you reveal who he is
having an affair with?
Will the lawsuit happen soon?
The next suit…
Ma'am.
Are you watching the news?
I laid the groundwork for you.
INCOMING CALL
SHIN HAE-RIN
When will you give me
the conclusive information?
You promised.
It has to be
an exclusive tip-off just to me.
What happened? I told you to make sure
she couldn't hire a lawyer.
How does she have a lawyer?
Well…
I apologize.
Find out who he is
and dig up anything you can find
to use against him.
Secretary Shin!
What do you think you're doing?
I told you not to show yourself.
Put your decision to fire me
on hold for now, please.
Until the situation is dealt with,
let me help until then.
My decision is final.
You're no longer my secretary.
Then from now on,
I'll do whatever I want.
What?
Secretary Shin?
From this point onward, whatever I do
has nothing to do with you.
I'm just doing it for my own sake.
Secretary Lee will be the witness.
You heard that?
I'm no longer related to this place
or the president-elect.
So you must not follow any of my orders.
Say something, sir.
Say she's wrong, please.
She's right.
She has nothing to do with us now.
Secretary Shin.
PRESIDENTIAL TRANSITION TEAM
SHIN HAE-RIN
No, that's not true at all.
It's fake news
that he cheated on his wife.
Spouse at fault? No.
It's not true that
the lawsuit concerns him
as the spouse at fault.
Ms. Cha is waiting.
Thank you.
This way.
VICTIM: CHA SU-YEON
ASSAILANT: YOON KI-JU
SETTLEMENT AGREEMENT
You dealt with the reporters well,
considering it was your first time.
Not too much, not too little.
Most of all, you looked reliable.
That's most important
in representing me legally from now on.
But do you really
want me to take on your divorce lawsuit?
Didn't you already agree to it?
That you'd take on my divorce suit
if I settled Ki-ju's case.
You took care of
Ji-yu's case as well
by digging into those girls' past.
The press conference went well too.
What's the matter?
Well, still…
No matter how I think about it,
divorce case isn't my specialty.
"Seon" in your name Kang Seon-ho.
You said it meant "vicious."
I need a lawyer who will fight viciously.
It's against the President.
And it is me who made him president.
I'll stir up the public opinion first.
That is politicians' weakest spot.
The public opinion
which changes multiple times a day.
Even more so now that he's the President.
The target of the reporters
will change from me to him.
They'd feel a bigger sense of achievement
if they attacked
the President who was having an affair
than his wife who bugged him for it.
He's the one
who provided the cause for it,
so they can say they're serving justice.
They'll attack him as much as they did me,
so they'll think it's fair to do so.
The election was only a month ago.
Will the public sway?
There's one thing I learned
about the public sentiment.
The public
isn't just a number.
They're live people.
Cha Su-yeon!
-Out!
Look at her, she's so thick-skinned.
She's shameless.
You should be ashamed.
Look at her standing tall
with her head held high.
Exactly.
Unbelievable.
She's coming out.
-Cha Su-yeon!
Who are you to stop us?
You don't understand us.
-What did we do wrong?
-Get out of my way!
Let me go!
Let them go.
It's okay, leave them be.
These people
are my family.
For over a decade, they've supported me
and given me more love
than I ever deserve. They're my family.
As a mom, and as a daughter,
I have something to say to my family.
Please give me some time.
Please set up a tent
to shelter them from the rain.
Yes, ma'am.
My goodness.
I'm sorry.
I did something terrible.
I disappointed you all.
The public isn't just a number.
They're live people.
I'm not here
as the wife of the president-elect
or the First Lady.
I'm here as a bad mom
and an immature daughter
who broke her family's hearts.
The betrayal and anger that you,
my family, must've felt from my actions…
I can't dare to fathom.
But I'll accept whatever punishment I get.
Don't worry
about me entering the Blue House
and acting like the First Lady
when I don't deserve it.
You can scold me for my faults
as much as you like.
But please.
Although it's spring, it's still chilly.
If you want to scold me,
please do so under the tent
where you can avoid the rain.
I'm sorry.
I'm very sorry.
It was terrible of me.
I'm sorry.
You're wrong.
As you said, we're family.
Families don't do that to each other.
She's right.
You're my family,
and so is she.
This student is my family too.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Thank you, Bo-ra.
I wanted to return this to you.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
And thank you.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
And thank you.
People are always angry.
They always look for someone
to take it out on.
What will happen
if the angry sentiment is
pointed at the President?
When the balloon is
this close to bursting,
we just have to prick it gently
with a needle called affair.
Isn't that the same for them, though?
If they make the same move,
people will criticize you badly.
I've been criticized more than enough.
But
they won't be able to handle it.
Because they've never fought so brutally
against the public.
Up until now,
I was the one who dealt with it.
Still, he's your husband.
He's your family.
Yes, he is my family.
A family…
is always a nuisance.
You wouldn't know.
I have one too.
My family.
HASEONG DETENTION CENTER
-You came.
-It must've been hard for you.
What happened?
Let's go. I'll explain on the way.
It breaks and goes bad easily.
Not to mention the stench when it does.
Come to think of it, a family
is very much like tofu.
Enough with your nonsense.
You'll take on the divorce lawsuit?
Why?
She got you out of jail,
and she pays me handsomely.
Everyone is watching it.
Why would I say no?
You sound very excited.
See that?
My friends
and even my old girlfriends from college
are texting me now that I'm famous.
She got her nose done.
It looks good.
Exactly, why would the other lawyers
have turned down such a good offer?
It's obvious.
What lawyer wouldn't want
to get in Hyun Min-cheol's good books?
And you don't want to?
What if Min-cheol wants you on his side?
Uncle. You must've forgotten,
but I'm a lawyer.
What if he promises you a position
for betraying Cha Su-yeon?
I already signed the attorney contract.
I'll lose my lawyer license if I do that.
What if in return for losing it,
he'll hand you a better position?
Then why did you do that?
Do what?
I heard that after Uncle Tae-hun died,
she visited you several times.
Why did you turn her down
when she asked for your help?
I turned down Cha Su-yeon's offer.
She said if I stopped
making an issue of the late Tae-hun,
she'd do everything for me,
and I rejected her dirty hands.
But you want to be her lawyer.
You'll hold her dirty hands. Am I wrong?
Being her lawyer doesn't mean
I'll become one of her people.
After I beat Hyun Min-cheol
in the lawsuit,
who would be next?
My final goal…
is Cha Su-yeon.
Can you even beat Min-cheol?
Can you even win?
Lawyers wouldn't be the only ones.
Everyone in their right mind in Korea
would have joined hands with Min-cheol.
Can you really defeat him?
It's Cha Su-yeon
who will go in the ring to fight.
HASEONG MEMORIAL PARK
Why are we here?
It's the anniversary
of Uncle Tae-hun's death today.
Grandma told me
to bring you straight here.
Here.
Who picked this suit?
Why? You don't like it?
I don't like the color.
You can't say that. You wear
the factory jacket all year round.
Hey.
I have a lot of clothes.
Fine, fine. I get it, so…
Let's go now.
Fine, let's go.
ROT IN HELL, ARSONIST
LATE DO TAE-HUN
Grandma, what's all this?
Heavens will punish them.
I thought they'd stopped,
but they did this again.
Give me that. I'll do it.
Heavens will punish them.
Was framing an innocent person not enough?
Mom, we'll do it. Get some rest.
My poor Tae-hun.
He's wronged even after his death.
Mom, stop. You'll collapse at this rate.
You damn brat.
How could you end up in a detention center
of all places?
Oh, dear.
My Tae-hun.
My poor Tae-hun.
Darn it. Let's go.
They're so thick-skinned.
They dare come here?
-You--
-Calm down. Don't do it.
Let's just go.
They all lost their family
at the same time.
Didn't we lose our family too?
Why must Tae-hun be treated
as an arsonist?
Why must he be treated as a sinner?
They need someone to resent for it.
Others might not understand that,
but we should.
For 15 years,
they shared the same grief
on the same day.
The same goes for him
who lost both his parents overnight.
MURDERER
LATE DO TAE-HUN
You brat.
Yes.
My dear.
It's okay.
He believed without a doubt
that Tae-hun had killed his parents.
When he belatedly found out
he was wrong, he was very shocked.
You saw it too.
I'm concerned about him.
He wants to avenge his parents,
but he might get hurt
by the lawsuit against Min-cheol.
Coming from the one who went wild
trying to avenge Tae-hun's death?
It's not the same.
Seon-ho isn't even 30 yet.
He has a bright future.
That's how furious he must feel.
You of all people should understand him.
That's why I'm worried about him.
You must protect him.
So that they can't hurt him.
LATE KANG IN-KYU, LATE SONG IN-KYEONG
THEIR ELDEST SON, KANG SEON-HO
CHA SU-YEON
KANG SEON-HO
It's me, Cha Su-yeon.
Are the preparations going smoothly?
What we need is evidence.
Proving the defendant's wrong
and providing physical evidence
will be the key.
Don't worry.
I'll get the evidence for you.
Can you at least give me
a heads up about the evidence?
You'll find out soon.
It's evidence he could never refute.
Just think about how to win the case
using that evidence.
Don't worry about it.
Evidence he could never refute…
It's going to be mud-slinging anyway,
so fight as dirty as you can.
Whether you win or lose,
you both lose in the end.
I wish to speak to the First Lady.
Unbelievable. How dare you show up here?
What would happen
if these words got out to the world?
Give Su-yeon a chance.
She's the one who'll guarantee our safety,
not the president-elect.
What deal did you make with her?
Hey, Min-cheol,
did Tae-hun start the fire?
He's not a murderer!
What would you do in my shoes?
Who would you choose?
Subtitle translation by: Sunyoung Baek,
Yeeun Kim